http://www.dragonboat.net/privacy-policy.aspx

Privacy Policy
Ottawa Dragon Boat Festival is committed to the confidentiality of data received from donors, registrants, sponsors and participants while, in particular, respecting the right of personal privacy. The festival does not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding individuals and takes reasonable steps to store information in such a manner as to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. Personal Information of identified individuals will not be shared with anyone outside the festival except for the specific purposes for which it was collected and only with those who have a relationship with the festival of such a nature that the festival is satisfied that they will preserve the confidentiality of such Personal Information.
Information collected by us
It is not our intention to identify individuals who merely visit our website, other than by IP addresses.
Consent
At all times we strive to comply with the various privacy laws in force but we reserve the right to disclose any information which we, in our discretion, deem necessary to comply with the laws of any jurisdiction, to comply with any court documents requiring production including subpoenas, search warrants and court orders, or where we consider such disclosure is necessary for the purposes of public security or for the preservation of our or our sponsors' safety, rights or property.
By accessing this site, YOU CONSENT to our collection and use of information as set out in the foregoing Privacy Policy. By accessing this website, you agree to our Privacy Policy and you accept its terms, as they may be amended from time to time. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy and are not prepared to accept these terms in full, please do not access this website. Our Privacy Policy will be amended from time to time and may be updated even when the website is not. Your access to our website is your continuing acceptance of the Privacy Policy as it exists on the date of each access. Please ensure that you review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the site so that you remain current with its terms.
DON'T MISS THIS HOLIDAY'S SESSIONS WITH RIVER TOWN SAINTS, LEMON CASH, AMANDA RHEAUME & MORE!
M.T. WALKER - RING THOSE BELLS // THE HOLIDAY SESSIONS
With the holiday season u ...
Read more...
RIVER TOWN SAINTS FREE VIRTUAL CONCERT SAT. NOV. 28, 8:00 PM
THE TIM HORTONS OTTAWA DRAGON BOAT FESTIVAL PRESENTS AN EVENING WITH RIVER TOWN SAINTS AND SPE ...
Read more...
Read all news...
Stay In Touch
Sign up for our newsletter and stay up to date with the latest information about the festival.
Sign Up Now!
© 2008 - 2020 Ottawa Dragon Boat Festival. All rights reserved. Disclaimer / Privacy Policy / Sitemap
Powered by EnvisionUP.
